I just wanted to show you quickly about this black bean.
This is a hard black bean, it has not been cooked, it is really quiet small compared to the pinto bean.
That is one of the reasons why it cooks so quickly is that it is much much smaller.
Today we are cooking this black bean in a pressure cooker.
I have just done a quick soak with it.
We have emptied all the water out and put the bean that we just cooked for 2 minutes and we went ahead and put it back in the pressure cooker with 6 cups of water.
We are going to go ahead and bring it up to 15 pounds of pressure, cook it for about 10 minutes.
Just let it sit there on the stove without the burner on or anything for about 10 minutes.
These would be done and I really hope that you would be motivated to run out and make some black bean salsa it so good.
It is a great dinner for tonight.
Thank you so much.